



35 Hemlock Circle, Cranford, New Jersey 07016 | (908) 499-2859 | mark@koellmann.eu

Sι	INA	IN/	ΙΛ	DV

Enthusiastic, people orientated and determined. Knowledge in a variety of technologically centered fields including creative media and project management.

## **S**KILLS

SKILLS				
Project Management	Working with a team towards a goal, organizing responsibilities, creating and following timelines.			
Software	Latest versions of Windows OS, Microsoft Office, Premiere Pro, After Effects, Photoshop, Illustrator and a variety of social media platforms.			
Languages	Fluent in German and English, writing and speaking. Lived in both countries for more than 9 years.			
Video/ Photography	Capable of using a variety of cameras along with lighting and audio equipment. Able to take an idea and turn it into a final product.			
EXPERIENCE				
2012-2015	Head Webmaster, Cranford High School Webmaster Team			
	-Project manager, lead designer/programmer.			
2011-Present	Owner, Koellmann.co			
	-Web-development, video production, photography, social media marketing.			
2014	Dental Assistant, Dr. Silverman DMD			
	-Internship; cleaning and maintaining dental supplies and upkeep of technology around the office. Ran a website and marketing campaign.			
2012-2016	Golf Counselor, West 9 Golf Course			
	-Summer time golf instruction. Certified First Tee coach. Volunteer for First Tee's junior golf program.			
2016	Accounting Intern, Epcos AG			
	-Worked in AP and AR, hands on learning with SAP and other databases, put in charge of reorganizing the sample kit assembly process.			

## **E**DUCATION

2015	High School Diploma, Cranford High School
2014	Deutsches Sprach Diplom II, Deutche Sprachschule
2019	Bachelor of Science in Management Information Systems, Rochester Institute of Technology